Warren,
I don't know how much you've been privy
to.
We're trying to get contract testing kind
of proven out a little bit more.
We were looking,
Franz has done a lot of work around it.
He's been building a skill to facilitate
contract testing.
If you don't know what contract testing
is,
I'm not going to get into that here
because it would take the entire hour.
And so do your research.
That sounded really rude,
but I didn't mean it that way.
I just meant like we don't have time for
Oh, yeah, we're good on that side.
Right, we should be.
that. Okay, good.
I didn't mean that that way, but.
That sounds very political and rude at
the same time.
But I see a lot of benefit in the
microservices architecture and having
contract tests set up.
I think it would be most valuable with
the CE services that are.
constantly having their contracts break,
but they don't have time to implement it.
And GRC is always on the forefront and
very agreeable to trying things out that
we think will benefit the team.
So that's what we started here.
We had agreed on setting up with a warm
level at first, so it's not.
dating anything,
so it's not blocking anything,
so we can kind of try it out and kind of
see if it's too much, too little,
and scale it back or, you know,
kind of adjust until we're ready to fully
turn on the contract and have it be a
breaking, a breaking contract, breaking.
Breaking gate,
I'm not sure how to reference that, um,
so...
Anyway,
so I talked to Jeff and talked to Franz a
little bit. And remind me, Jeff,
which services you were hoping to
implement the contract between consumer
producer.
Right. I mean,
if we scope it to the GRC or the, yeah,
Yeah.
I think it was going to be the GLS
Library Service and Policy Manager.
Thanks.
I can check my pull requests real quick.
Yeah.
Okay.
Welcome, Gio.
Yeah, looks like Content Library Service,
Policy Manager, be good candidates,
Yes.
Oh.
GRC Library Service.
My team has familiarity with those.
Yeah.
Okay, and which one's the consumer,
which one's the producer?
I, I'd have to look and see.
Okay.
They both sent and received messages.
Does anybody find, like,
Yeah.
do you have the login to the packed
server handy?
Because we could log in and read all this
information.
I had that all set up when I set this
aside. Yeah, but if you share your screen.
Yeah, hold on.
Yeah.
We should be able to...
Thanks.
Sid.
View the contracts. Yeah, there we go.
So there's the answer to your question.
So policy manager is a consumer of the
content scheduler.
The GRC is a consumer of Policy Manager.
It.
Yeah.
Help.
So we have consumers on the left-hand
side, providers on the right-hand side,
and then links to the actual contracts.
here in the center.
Mm-hmm.
If.
I don't think it would be, once we get...
get it implemented in a couple of
services that were in control.
So it wouldn't be much of an effort to
make a pull request into the three C's to
at least have them publish their
contracts.
That shouldn't negatively impact them in
any way. And it would.
Y.
propagate the contracts that other
services could then read.
I don't think we have to wait for them
because they're too busy. I mean,
that's the whole,
the downside of this particular
implementation of contract testing.
Like everybody's going to always be too
busy. So I was, I think.
I'd be curious to hear the solution of
when people will not be busy enough to
actually implement this properly. Like,
do we have the organizational maturity to
Right.
Yeah.
commit to this?
And if teams are saying we're too busy,
to me,
that's an indicator that we lack the
organizational maturity.
to potentially even start with this.
Exactly.
That's why GRC is a prime candidate to
kind of pilot this and I think.
I think it'll be like a C, you know,
see all the value they're providing,
kind of a thing that you guys often do
for the rest of the org, where, you know,
it's a sort of a proven process that is
saving you all time,
and then other teams will fall in line
when they see that value.
I think,
I don't want to get too far deep into it,
but I think they don't realize that
putting the work in up front will save
them so much time.
even like, not even down the line,
but like midline, you know,
by giving them that feedback.
Because right now the only gate that we
truly have that's stopping things from
deploying is that Cypress gate.
And that is not like that's way too late
in the process.
That should not be our one and only way
of.
detecting me if there is a contract
breaking because it is not an API test at
all. So I think, anyway,
I think we're going on the right path and
I think I'll get them to kind of agree to
it a little bit further down the line.
But this is this POC.
Care.
Got it. Yeah, I mean,
the other thing I needed to know would be,
you know,
there's a couple different ways to
implement.
The.
The packed broker into the ADL pipelines.
I think they had like different.
jewels of
Mm.
adoption.
I think there's like platinum or gold and
Yeah.
diamond and so I'd have to see.
I was hoping we would have someone from
Yeah.
your team, Malia,
like identify what our end state is
Yeah.
regarding implementation.
So as we're implementing the POC.
I would know that we're moving in the
direction that you signed off on.
Yeah.
I think.
Is gold what we're going for?
Is that why we have this nice AI
generated?
How can you tell it's AI generated?
I was hand drawing this. Come on.
What is this like?
Yeah.
Hand shading it on your iPad with your
Apple Pencil.
Haha.
Yeah.
Wow.
I handcrafted the prompt. Come on. Yeah,
so I think gold is what we think might be
Okay.
good enough and provide enough value,
even though it's not capable of gaining.
Okay.
Yeah.
But I think that's a good place to start
without it being too ambitious.
Okay.
And so I just wanted to make you aware,
you can take a screenshot of this if you
Yeah.
want,
but I'm going to move away from this page
here real quick.
There is a contract testing.
Yeah.
repository now that just serves as
something that Copilot scaffolded it out.
And also the third link I sent in chat is
a contract testing skill.
It's quite large.
I had Copilot gather all the information
that he possibly could from all of the
different sources to generate.
all the information.
And this basically just serves as a
vehicle for asking questions.
I've found that the best way for me to
learn and understand the sequence of
events is to have this skill.
It sits in AI skills, by the way.
Just pull it in and ask all the questions.
Yeah.
that you have that are kind of hard to
understand who is in charge of what,
who owns what,
when does the consumer ask for the
contract,
does that come before the producer,
et cetera, et cetera.
And so I had lots and lots of questions
and this skill is pretty good at
answering them all.
And so the contract testing here
illustrates a lot of stuff,
including how let's say a consumer would
go about writing the tests.
Great examples here on.
I particularly like this format here,
you use the pack builder with extension
methods going upon receiving a request to
get all products given products exist
with requests to this API endpoint will
respond with this status,
with this header.
And so these are very clean.
The.
Let you know that these...
couple of resources are out there.
No, it.
Yeah, I mean,
I would say the first expectation I would
Yeah.
have of a AI skill would be...
You know,
show me what the approved way to modify
In.
an existing ADO CICD pipeline to
introduce the hacked publication step,
Yeah.
and then maybe optionally.
Yeah.
The subsequent step to block that same
pipeline if a contract doesn't exist that
this service depends on.
I think that would...
This is.
Yeah,
the skills should be able to answer all
those things for you.
Okay, I mean, is it going to tell me,
like,
what about like authenticating with the
packed broker? Like,
do we have org level secrets,
like the login and password that the
pipeline would need to publish to our
packed broker?
Probably not,
but that would be a natural evolution of
Okay.
what you would go about implementing.
It.
Yeah,
so it'd be nice if that was something
that your team was able to provide for us
so we could just, you know,
you guys are making the cookie cutter and
I'm just having a dev come in and say,
okay, run this skill on this pipeline.
It should, you know,
Yeah.
inject this step in the correct sequence
and it should reference these.
secrets and it should just like create a
pull request that gets this entire
pipeline up to the publication phase at
least.
And then maybe a second AI skill prompt.
Yeah,
I'd be happy to work with you on that
rather than soloing it and inventing A
pipeline on my own because you already
Mm-hmm.
have something in mind and I'd be happy
to assist there.
Yeah, that's fine.
I think I would say in general for
adoption,
it's kind of like the advice I gave,
I think, on a previous topic.
Maybe it was your set at free loop.
It's like,
I think if you come to the teams with,
we all know you all have standardized on
the golden path template,
The.
here's some tooling that perfectly
interacts or is compatible with it.
No.
that would like ease adoption.
I hear that, Jeff,
but I think if we can come together
But...
halfway and create our first sort of like
POC,
then that could serve as that golden
example.
Yeah.
Then I can take that back into this
contract testing as a couple of ADO
Yeah.
pipeline examples.
Okay, yeah, that sounds good.
I think that would that would increase
Yeah.
your probability of success.
Yeah.
It's.
I guess the other thing I was curious
about is I, as I'm looking at this test.
I mean,
is there any reason we should not use
like the wreck and roll language format
here? I mean,
it looks like they're trying to go for
like a natural language.
I mean, you can, you can adopt it.
Test expression.
Okay.
I have never written a single line of
rack'n'roll, so I don't know.
It's the Gurkan language,
it's just a natural kind of.
Okay.
Language that.
Yeah.
Yeah, when's it something?
But I guess I don't know how flexible the
Pack Builder Service is here, so...
Okay.
Yeah, that that's like an optional thing.
The.
Let's just play around with it.
To answer your question, no,
that thing is not flexible. Yeah, those,
Yeah.
I.
so those, those dots,
those are actual method calls on Pack
Got it.
The.
Builder.
Yeah,
mess one of those up or the order in
which he put those and it'll break.
Got it. Yeah, that's okay.
I get that's I don't want to
I can explore that idea on my own time.
We'll leave it at that.
You can you can create like a Jeff Buda
version of backed builder and.
Right, I'll fork it tonight.
Yeah.
Channels.
There was one other library that somebody
mentioned about contract testing.
Did we evaluate whatever that one was to
see if it would be a little bit easier
for teams to adopt?
I can't remember the name of it,
which is going to make this conversation
difficult.
And.
Are you talking about as a POC?
Yeah,
it was like a someone mentioned a
contract testing solution that was not
packed.
net and I was just curious if we did any
research to see if there are other
Yeah.
contract testing solutions that might
provide some benefit.
Yeah.
So I don't know what the other names of
the contract testing solutions are,
but I will say that Christian and
Accenture did a deep dive into a bunch of
The.
contract testing solutions.
I want to say there's a confluence page
of like all the different ones,
and then PAC was the one that worked.
Yeah.
One,
there was some sort of like research done.
Okay, I can leave it at that.
Yeah.
Granted, that was probably.
Two, three years ago now,
but you know that that research was done,
Yeah.
so...
Understood.
Yeah, I did look over that.
It was very high.
Hey, Daddy.
I'm just kidding.
Got a special, special guest.
That was Gio.
Geo, are you sucking on a helium balloon?
Anyway.
No,
you're listening to my son talk in the
background.
Yeah, no, I figured. Yeah,
if it's my house,
Yeah.
you're going to hear a dog barking,
so we all have our distractions at home.
Yes,
I did read over what Christian and
Accenture produced,
and it was very high level,
so there wasn't like a whole lot of...
I mean,
it was great to like get yourself well
versed in contract testing,
but I don't think there was a whole lot
of practical application there for us.
I honestly think that you, Jeff,
and Gio have done probably more work than
we can reuse than anyone else.
Sam.
So...
Um...
Yeah, I mean,
so it sounds like you're just hoping that
our team will pick this up and update our
pipelines to publish.
It.
IT.
Is that the implication I'm getting?
Yes.
I would love to be injected into that
process so I can learn how you guys are
Yeah.
doing it and which pipelines you're
working on and just pull me in on a few
What?
working sessions so I can get the
takeaways, et cetera.
Yeah.
Yeah,
I think there would be a lot of value in
us doing a working session,
like maybe not with any people that would
put their fingers on the keyboards to get
it done.
And that way we can learn from the
experience and then take that to other
teams. So I don't want it to be like, hey,
we're going to pass this off to you,
just produce it.
I want it to be something we all learn
from.
and produce something in the end that's
legitimate.
Okay.
You know, effective.
Um, yeah, I'm happy to...
put a bit of time into that if Warren is
okay with it. The PRS I made,
Yeah.
I just made on my own weekend and evening
time.
So I'll have to defer to Warren's wisdom.
But yeah, right from the jump,
we would need like a org secret for the
packed broker URL.
The packed broker username and packed
broker password.
I think that's the only viable way for
this to be deployed across multiple.
pipelines and maintained. But yeah.
I think you are, actually,
I think on last check,
not that I want you to do it,
but it's as simple as just if you have
the credentials.
Mhm.
You have the rights to just store them on
the org level.
Yeah,
I'm fine creating them myself if that's
the way we want to go.
I guess I don't want to unilaterally.
I can,
I'll be happy to create them too if you
want me to.
I just need the names of the variables
Okay.
and the values and then that's a
two-minute thing.
I, I...
True, yeah, I agree.
I guess I just wanted to make sure that I
wasn't acting unilaterally and whatever I
was doing was aligned with the end goal.
Understood.
Yeah.
But sure.
I think we're just exploring our way into
our first solution where we get gold
Okay.
level working on both sides,
on the consumer and the other side,
8.
and then...
The.
We'll just then we have something that we
can either take back into the contract
Yeah.
testing as the demo and sort of like the
frame of reference or whether that's.
Yep.
Just go look in this repo. I don't really,
I'm not married to a solution there.
Okay.
Got it. Yeah, I'm happy to help.
I think my,
Yeah.
IT.
probably my policy manager pull request
would be a good place to start.
All right,
do you mind just quickly copy-pasting
that?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
It looks like it has reasonable looking.
Yeah.
Changes to the pipelines already,
and then it has an example test.
S.
for a message.
Yeah, I can do that.
I'll put it in the meeting chat. So maybe.
Okay.
Can review that and see what you think.
And.
So I'm curious to defer to Warren.
You know,
I don't want to like assume that this is
this fits into your.
your, you know, sprint or a sprint.
So I'm just curious to hear your thoughts
on the whole thing and whether it fits.
Yeah,
so my personal opinion is that I've been
a part of the conversation trying to get
packed flow, packed broker,
Yeah.
some sort of contract testing going for a
while. So I'm very pro helping out,
but to the point of capacity. I mean,
that's why I'm attending here today is
Yeah.
just to get an idea of.
Okay.
Like,
what level of work are we actually
Yes.
talking? You know,
I'm more than happy to have Jeff and Gio
But.
Yeah.
help out a little bit here and there,
but we don't necessarily have...
A ton of capacity to be spending on this.
It.
Sure.
I think, go ahead, sorry. Well,
I was going to say,
I mean, if we did that, go ahead, Jeff.
No, I was...
I think because the PRs exist already,
to me,
the next step would be to have Geo and
Franz review this pull request and...
Really, that's about it.
There's not much here.
George.
So let me,
so just to understand this correctly,
which is this representing,
this is only representing one side of the
Yeah.
story though, right?
Sure, yeah, I have 4 pull requests.
I just picked this one. To me,
it looks pretty low risk. So we've got,
we've hooked in the packed broker server
IT.
to the pull request pipeline,
the build pipeline. Then we've got, yeah,
Yeah.
if you look at it this way,
it's like 2 pipelines were changed.
I added a whole.
Yeah.
contract testing assembly,
and this is just updating the solution
file to acknowledge that there's a new
project. So I think we're pretty close.
We would need to add the secrets we
discussed.
You know, yes.
Yeah,
but the hardest part for me is to wrap my
head, because you have to remember,
you're knee deep into this every day.
Mhm.
And to me,
policy manager is just an arbitrary repo
name. I don't know how it relates.
Is it the consumer? Is it the...
Yeah.
Well, yeah, in that case,
just I'd refer you to that page you were
sharing earlier to see what contracts it
is and if it's a producer or consumer.
In my mind, because I am so close to it,
it produces and consumes lots of messages,
but in the context of this POC,
I think that pack
Dot net page that you had up,
Franz would be the best answer to your
question.
Yeah, am I not sharing anymore? I guess.
No, you are. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I took it over. Yeah.
I just haven't logged in.
I'll stop sharing.
I just haven't logged into that server in
No, no, that's great.
a while.
But maybe while you do that,
I'll just speak to Warren. So I mean,
Let's see.
Warren, there's not much risk here.
There's no change to production code.
The.
The worst case scenario would be that
either our build pipeline would be down
Yeah.
for a bit.
I think we can verify the PR pipeline in
the context of my pull request.
So I wouldn't expect there to be any risk
there.
So it seems like because it's already
implemented, it should be a low risk,
The.
low effort first step,
at least on the policy manager side.
I would think we could get something
working in about a day of Geo or my
effort.
Um, just, just on that side, so...
I'm looking at the YAML and it does,
it just kind of logs the result and then
moves on,
even if it breaks somewhere in that
The.
process.
So I think the risk is even lower than
your than your image.
Yeah, it's quite low. Yeah,
I was going to, as a first step,
I need to double check,
but I was going to make sure that the new
steps in the YAML files were like Warren
only.
Yeah.
So even if we get something wrong in the
initial phases,
it would not impede Warren's.
Yeah.
deployment cadence,
we would just see a warning like, oh,
I couldn't log into the packed broker or
oh,
the URL is wrong or something to that
effect. So I was going for a very.
conservative,
gradual approach to putting these changes
in. But yeah, to me,
it seems like all we need is to add some
Yeah.
secrets,
have Geo and Franz look over this pull
request, and then.
merge it in and see what happens.
And that would do it for policy manager.
And then, so Franz, who's the,
can you refresh my memory using the
documentation? Who's the consumer? Was it,
was it, did I do GRC?
Oh, so.
It looks like...
So, consumers policy,
so we that's the policy major one,
policy manager.
so then the next one.
Sid.
Yeah.
Policy.
We got.
Content Scheduler.
CM Core Content Scheduler.
Content scheduler would be more valuable.
I definitely look in my pull request and
see.
I think I know that their teams don't
have capacity as we discussed,
but I'm I think.
G or I could.
put in a conservative pipeline change
that would at least publish their
contracts with low risk of disruption to
their deployment cadence.
The.
I mean, ideally,
we want to see it log that there was a
broken contract,
and then then we get that feedback.
So we want something that will,
that breaks regularly.
Yeah, well, break,
I'm gonna go no on break,
but I do think we can tell ADO that if
the can I deploy command of pact.
net fails,
we can log that to ADO as like a little
Yeah.
warning icon. There's ADO.
build step result that is worn.
So they won't see the pretty green circle.
Okay.
They'd see like a,
I think it's like a yellow one that
Yeah.
indicates there was a acceptable but not
clean run of that.
I.
Storage.
Um...
So yeah, we could, that would be...
That's what I would recommend.
Start with Policy Manager and move on to.
The other one would be the GRC,
like my team and Gio are very familiar
with the GRC, so we could,
let me pull up my GRC pull request.
One moment.
CE.
Um, Jeff, why are you pulling that up? Um,
Malia, I
Mhm.
understand what you want.
Like if this thing is,
No.
if a contract is broken,
the pipeline fails, and then we fix it,
which is ideally what we would want.
But on the other side,
You.
if teams are saying we don't have time to
implement this, once we do that.
Time or not,
they will need to know how to do pack,
because once it breaks,
you got to know how to fix it.
Yeah, no, I was, I was like...
So an easy way to make them have time is
to add the contract gating,
and then time or not,
they will need to make some.
Yeah.
I, I really agree with that.
I was actually, I was suggesting that we..
.
Set that warning or even log that the
contract is broken, let them move on,
you know, until we get that feedback,
we know it's working,
and then we start kind of escalating the
the reaction to the contract breaking
into to the point where people are used
to if it's broken, like...
All hands on deck,
someone's got to fix it,
which is down the line for us until we
cut through the value.
I wasn't suggesting we start there.
But that's I don't think.
No, yeah, I, I, I know, I know that.
I'm just,
I'm just laying out the the framework,
because just because, like,
the whole thought on this is if people
don't know how to use it,
just because the pack worker says this is
broken doesn't mean it actually is. Like,
if you deploy the producer before the
consumer, if you're changing contract,
Right.
it'll say it's broken because you went
the wrong way, like the wrong order.
Yeah.
even like, so it's like, you know,
part of this is just a upskilling level
Yeah.
up type of thing.
Even if we decide what the contract does
again,
people will still have to know how to use
it, essentially.
So that's all I was calling out.
Yeah, and I think...
We have a fair amount of trial and error
to go through before we're ready to
expose this to people that don't
necessarily understand contract testing
and how things have to be set up.
And like,
I don't think we're ready to get people
involved who don't get the big picture.
Yeah,
the other thing I'd considered along
IT.
those lines is an org secret that the new
contract testing build stages would
monitor that was like effectively a kill
switch. So like if...
If the pack server goes down or the
underlying database gets corrupted and we
Okay.
know that the pack stages of all these
pipelines will not be successful,
I was envisioning an org level disable
packed net so that all of the...
Yeah.
pipelines that we've modified would
effectively just have no op.
Yeah.
No.
Another example of a thing I want to
avoid,
in the past we've had Sonar Cloud go down
and break lots of pipelines for a day.
Yeah.
So we'd want to have,
that's a proposal to the group would be a
Yeah.
kill switch that we could seamlessly
disable this if it goes pear-shaped for
some reason.
You.
Question is,
should that be taken here about the
Yeah.
nuance? You could.
You.
potentially, you know,
like when you set an org level variable
It.
and then you set a repo level variable
with the same name,
you're basically creating an override. So.
Whether,
where should it sit at the org level or
What?
should it sit at the repo level?
I don't know. If, yeah.
Yeah,
I was thinking at org level just so we
IT.
could turn it off for everybody.
Like if we know the server's broken.
We just,
we don't want people to have to go in and
modify dozens of pipelines when the
packed net server is down for a couple
But.
No, yeah, yeah,
I totally see the value in that,
days. OK, OK.
but I was just wondering if one team had
their pipeline broken for whatever reason,
they could bypass it with an org repo
level override or, you know,
just have it set there, I don't know,
to disable it.
Mhm.
Edds.
I think another group decision as I'm
recollecting some nuance of my PRs is I
The.
think if you go, if you share, Franz,
if you go back to the UI,
Help.
Okay.
I thought I introduced the idea that
there are multiple environments and each
environment might have.
a different version of the contract.
There is, I think, but first of all,
I got, yeah,
Ohh.
Did you see that?
I've seen environments defined somewhere,
but before, how do you, like, how do you,
Okay.
this naming here,
I just can't figure out what messaging
means in terms of on the repo level.
Ohh...
Well,
policy manager messaging just corresponds
Is it?
to the policy manager repo. That's all.
Okay.
It.
I'm not exactly sure why it threw
messaging at the end of all of those,
Ohh.
but yeah,
the GRC library maps to the GRC repo.
And that might be like, yeah,
maybe we don't know that yet.
I guess maybe that's something we have to
wait and see. But as you can imagine,
Yeah.
as these...
Contractors are evolving over time.
Different environments will have
different versions of the contract and.
Um, that's like another detail,
and I think we would get maximum value if
Yeah.
we...
acknowledge that we need to store the
version of the contract per environment.
Yeah.
So we know, oh,
this can be promoted to staging or this
But...
is in staging but can't go to prod.
You know, pretty OK.
Yeah,
that was actually an original problem
Mmh.
with the ADR that I think Christian
initially proposed that there would be a
pack broker host for each environment.
Mm.
Yes.
which is an anti-pattern.
So since this supports it,
Yeah.
Sid.
I just haven't found where we actually
set that.
Help.
Yeah, I'll, like I said,
I'll refresh my memory. I saw,
No problem.
Yeah.
I saw a mention of it in the...
in my pipeline changes.
Yeah, it's built into Pacnet.
It's called the...
Yeah, it is.
The contract matrix.
Yeah.
It's very hard to follow when you read
documentation. They use a lot of foobars,
but it's...
Yeah.
And it does say like right in this radio
button, it mentions the version.
It's it there.
But.
So it's possible I just didn't seed the
matrix with enough data.
And I see a version number drop down
there too, Franz,
Of.
so maybe what I'm talking about is here.
But it's probably because I just didn't
Yeah, that didn't, that didn't do it.
That didn't do it.
seed the database with enough.
Oh.
variations to the contract.
Like I think I just manually pushed up
The.
the latest version of each contract,
but maybe that's something we can
It.
discover.
So Warren says that we aim to see if we
can get it running by the end of the
quarter. Shouldn't take too much time.
Yeah, sorry,
you're stopping to read it anyways. Yeah,
Okay.
I need to drop,
but I'm on board with supporting this if
we feel like we can get those merged and
get some basic MVP up logging by the end
Thank you.
of the quarter.
Sounds to me from what you're saying,
Do you want to?
Jeff, that shouldn't be too hard.
I'm okay if we,
Yeah.
if I'm okay if we can push further, but...
Open.
you know,
we've got probably some policy plan stuff
Yeah.
that Magic Strings will need to help get
into and clean up as well later in the
quarter if we have excess capacity.
So we'll have to play it by ear,
Help.
but I'm okay, you know,
with us helping move this forward. So.
It.
Oh.
Okay, thanks Warren.
Appreciate your support.
Okay.
Thanks, you got an amazing team,
by the way.
Yeah, I like them.
Yeah.
Bye.
Well,
someday you'll have to explain that to me,
Uh...
Warren, but okay.
Smoke.
Yes.
Franz, I mean,
you're always welcome to come back to my
Ha ha.
It's most, it's mostly Jeff.
team. You're always welcome to come back.
Hey, no poaching.
Yeah.
It's always,
always good to have a fallback option.
Yeah.
Thanks, Warren. Yeah.
You threaten to poach my people,
I threaten to poach yours.
Right.
Yeah.
All right, well,
what I'll do after this call is I'll
write up a task, I guess. I don't know,
is this capitalizable? Malia,
do you happen to know?
Oh yeah, for sure.
Oh, okay, all right. Well,
I'll write up a user story to adopt what
my 2 pull requests are doing.
So I'll make one for each,
Yeah.
one for policy manager, one for GRC.
Those 2 repos are completely within
Warren's area of responsibilities,
so we don't need.
manage real buy-in beyond what we already
have. So I'll make 2 user stories.
Yeah.
I'll refresh my memory on those pull
requests. You know, in the meantime,
Help.
maybe the people on the call could review
them and give some initial feedback.
A
They're linked to in the meeting.
Chat,
and then we can we should be able to get
Yeah.
those merged in pretty pretty quickly.
From a testing perspective, you know,
there's no deployable code changes,
so I won't have to get through the
Yeah.
bottleneck that is, you know, my...
test engineers capacity and I won't have
to worry about the deployment bottleneck.
So it should go pretty quick once I get
them written up and I have these people
on the call review them.
And then maybe we could meet again in a
week or two to evaluate progress.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Just let us know when, you know,
Okay.
I don't know if you want to just use the
contract testing channel that's out there,
All right.
if you just want to reach out to all of
us, whatever. I guess.
Sure, we can use that.
I'll just use the contract. Yeah,
I'll use contract testing. Franz,
as an action item for you,
if you'd be so kind. Like,
I think it would be wise to make another
login. Like,
I think when I last I saw our pack.
net deployment only had one login,
which seems a bit risky.
Yes.
Like maybe,
I guess I'll defer to your wisdom,
write your skills wisdom on if we want to
make a second login that has write
permissions that the, you know,
the publisher steps of the pipeline can
But.
use to log in.
Yeah.
Yeah, I haven't dug in as deep as Gio had,
like,
Yeah.
because he stood up the whole thing about
a year ago, right?
Or maybe even a little longer ago, and...
Mhm.
So.
That's true.
Um...
Yeah, I don't know what kind of rights.
I just, you gave.
Be honest, I do not, you can click.
Yeah.
I don't remember if you can create,
I know you can create a read-only and a
write.
Login, I don't know if you can create.
I have to go back and check to see if you
can create multiple logins.
I just don't remember.
Okay. Yeah,
I guess I just assumed that they would
have different levels. Because, you know,
we need,
Yes.
Thank you.
eventually we'll need individual
contributors to be able to run the CLI
commands to fix up contracts. You know,
eventually we're going to have a breaking
contract.
and I predict that we'll need to allow.
individual contributors to have some sort
of access to that database to fix things
like, like, oh,
we deployed a version of the code.
We didn't update the packed server at
that time.
Yeah.
So now we have to retroactively go back
and correct some.
record in the packed database. All right,
well, I think that, I mean, go ahead.
Yeah.
I was just going to say,
I feel like there are probably a whole
lot of things downstream that we're going
to have to think about,
like debugging a broken contract,
things like that,
OK, yeah.
that we're not even wrapping our brains
around,
which is why I just kind of want to see
something break with a warning level,
of course, just to see,
just to start thinking through some of
the things.
different scenarios that we're going to
have to think through. But I'll try,
Okay.
maybe Franz,
you and I can brainstorm some of the
things that we'll need to think about on
the roadmap. Obviously,
documentation and stuff is one of those
things, but yeah,
we'll try to think ahead and envision
what we don't know yet.
Yeah.
Yeah,
the fact that we have a contract testing
repo,
we can do an FAQ in there and just kind
of expand upon it as we run into stuff
and...
Ohh.
Okay.
Um...
in different places. So,
but I would love to like maybe get a
Care.
meeting or two,
a working meeting or two on the calendar
Yeah.
for next week.
Um, yeah.
Sure.
If you can.
Yeah.
I'll defer to you.
Did I just find something on the calendar
that works for you? Let's see what day.
Yeah, but that works.
Okay.
How much?
Do you want like later?
How much time do you want before we meet
What was that?
again?
Oh, I don't think I need much time.
I'm hoping to do this asynchronously.
So to me,
the next steps are the people on this
call need to give me some initial code
review feedback.
I will go back and review the pull
requests myself. I mean,
it's possible we could merge in the
policy manager pull requests.
Tomorrow.
Yeah, I, I would,
I will create the org level variables and
Um...
Yeah.
But.
a kill switch,
so I just need the credentials.
Good circle.
You're breaking up there, Gio.
Yeah.
Consumer goes first.
Consumer,
I think he's saying consumer goes first.
Sorry, consumer goes first.
I think that doesn't matter in this case,
Joe,
Yeah.
The consumer was first.
because I manually use the CLI to seed
all the contracts, so I...
I think we could go in any order in this
initial effort, but I agree.
Consumer goes first is the architecture
that pack.net uses. The secrets.
Yeah.
All right, yeah,
why don't you schedule some time, Franz?
I think that would be the next step. Nick,
what role are you playing in this?
Yeah.
I am playing an assist role, anyway.
I see. OK,
so will you be will I be seeing you in
the in the working group meeting?
You?
I.
If it's pertaining to this, yes,
you should anticipate, yeah, me joining.
Okay, got it.
Okay, all right. Well, I mean,
I anticipate your pull request feedback.
Okay, cool. It's on my to-do list.
Cool.
Cool. Yep, I think that's all that I need.
It sounds like we've got some good.
See that.
But.
Steps forward.
Good.
Yeah.
Yeah, awesome.
I'll put something on the calendar for
next week.
Since it's more of a working session,
I'm not sure if you actually need me,
but I will listen in and be a sponge just
so I can understand a little better.
Okay.
Yeah, you can do that.
I think it also helped me, to be honest,
to just try to move forward in the
meantime asynchronously. So yeah, please,
please don't wait for that meeting to do
pull request feedback.
Yeah.
And I think it's possible that the policy
manager merge could happen before that.
Yeah.
But...
Meeting if all goes well,
so let's I would I would say working
Good.
asynchronously.
will get us the best results given how
busy everybody is with other projects and
How do you, how do you, how do you,
when you tinker around with these YAML
deliverables.
files in Azure DevOps,
how do you test these? Is it just pray?
It.
Um...
No, that's a fair question. You can,
especially the pull request one,
No.
It's a lot of prank.
You.
you can run it before it's merged. Yeah,
on that branch. I haven't.
Yep.
On the on the branch, right?
It.
And how safe is that if I wanted to try
that?
Let's say, yeah,
the pull request one doesn't do anything
aside from,
there's no side effects aside from
Okay.
determining if your pull request check
has succeeded or not.
The.
Okay.
So, good, good question, but yeah,
in the context of...
Yeah,
modifying the pull request one should be
very, very low risk.
Is that the one I'm sharing right now?
Just...
The.
Well, no, it's the one that's dash PR.
So there's,
if you look at your list of files changed,
policy-manager-pr.yaml.
Gotcha.
Sid.
Yeah.
Um, I'll, like I said,
I'll refresh my memory and I can share.
If I,
I'll try to run it this evening and see
what happens. I just don't quite recall.
I do have those secrets set up,
it looks like, in the repo.
So it should just...
It.
That shouldn't be a problem, you know.
IT.
Thank you.
for what we're trying to do with our
first two pull requests.
Oh.
Yeah,
I wouldn't be able to see the values of
them, though.
I would be able to utilize them,
Yeah, exactly. Yeah. But yeah,
you should be able to utilize them. Yeah,
but I can't. Yeah.
Care.
so.
Cool. Well, I appreciate you guys' time,
so...
Ohh.
Yeah, yep, that's all I have.
Yeah.
And thank you for always being
open-minded to, you know,
things that we're trying out and,
you know,
giving us honest feedback on everything
as well.
So we really appreciate that mentality.
Yeah.
Yep, no problem.
I appreciate you all being open to doing
this. And, you know, if we need to...
Oh, what's the word I'm looking for?
I guess if we need to socialize it,
I do feel like this directly contributes
to adopting AI generated code.
It.
Like we want to add as many guardrails as
possible so that the AI can generate code
Yeah.
that's correct.
So if anybody questions the...
The value of this, you know,
given how popular AI is these days,
But.
you know,
mentioning AI and this being an AI guard
rail is a good way to position it and to
hopefully explain to people unfamiliar to
CE.
it what its value is. Basically,
in my mind, it enables
more AI generated code. That's correct.
And it should enable more frequent and
more confident deployments,
which is another bottleneck that I'm
Yeah.
trying to solve.
It's absolutely key here,
like I couldn't preach this more.
Yep.
The more autonomous goals we have,
the more guardrails we need.
The.
I cannot get enough of those.
Yep.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Okay, well, I'll see you all in Slack,
I imagine, and then at our next meeting.
Yeah.
Baby.
Yeah.
Yeah, see you on Slack. That's inevitable.
Yeah, you too.
Right.
Yep. Have a nice evening, everybody.
Yep.
What?
Yes, thanks, Phil. I guess.
You too. Bye.
Yep, bye.
Bye.